Speaker 1: She has medium-length brown hair and she’s very tall and slim.
She’s quite shy.
Speaker 2: He has quite short wavy hair, it’s sort of red, and he has a small beard and a moustache.
He’s a really nice guy, very kind.
Speaker 1: She’s very talkative and funny.
She has curly grey hair, and she wears glasses.
Speaker 2: He has short blond hair and blue eyes.
He’s a big man, well-built, and he’s very tall.
He’s a great colleague – he’s really hard-working.
Speaker 1: She’s very extrovert and friendly.
She has very curly hair, not short, but not very long, and she has a beautiful smile.
Speaker 2: My granddad looks just like my dad.
He’s quite short, and he has short white hair and a bit of a beard – he doesn’t shave very often.
He’s really warm and open, and has lots of friends.
Speaker 1: She’s really attractive, and she’s a lovely person, very generous to her friends.
She’s medium height and she’s quite big.
She has fantastic hair, long and dark and braided.
Speaker 2: He isn’t very tall – in fact he’s quite short –
and he has a beard and a moustache and wavy brown hair.
He’s OK, but to be honest, I think he’s a bit mean.
He never pays when we go out!